Stephen Hess Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Brookings Institution, 1961-2016 (Box 1-70)
  - Reporter interviews
    - House, Karen Elliott, 1978, 2003-2010 (Box 38)
    - Houston, Paul, 1978, 1994 (Box 38)
    - Howard, Lucy, 1978, 2009 (Box 38)
    - Hughes, Thomas H., 1978 (Box 39)
    - Hume, Brit, 1978, 2005-2007 See also Container 63 and See also mss83739_163_003 (Box 39)
    - Humphries, Harrison, 1978, 1994 (Box 39)
    - Hunt, Albert R., 1978, 2005-2007 (Box 39)
    - Hunter, Marjorie, 1978, 2001 (Box 39)
    - Hyde, John, 1978, 2007-2009 (Box 39)
    - Independent writers, 1978-2011 (Box 39)
    - Irving, Macculloch, 1978, 2009 (Box 39)
    - Irwin, Don, 1978, 1991, 2008 (Box 39)
    - Jackson, Brooks, 1978, 2007 (Box 39)
    - Jackson, Robert, 1978, 2011 (Box 39)
    - Jackson, Stuart, 1978, 2006-2007 (Box 39)
    - Jaroslovsky, Rich, 1978, 1999-2008 See also mss83739_163_004 (Box 39)
    - Jones, Clayton, 1978, 2007 (Box 39)
    - Jones, Phil, 1978, 1999-2001 (Box 39)
    - Johnson, Mal, 1978, 2007 (Box 39)
    - Kahn, Helen, 1978, 1993, 2000 (Box 39)
    - Kalb, Bernard and Marvin L., 1978, 2006-2007 See also mss83739_163_033 (Box 39)
    - Kalb, Marvin L., 1978, 2006-2007 (Box 39)
    - Kaplow, Herb, 1978, 2002, 2008, 2013 (Box 39)
    - Karmin, Monroe, 1978, 1999, 2008 (Box 39)
    - Kaylor, Bob, 2007 (Box 39)
    - Keller, Bill, 1978, 2005-2011 (Box 39)
    - Kelly, Daniel, 1978 (Box 39)
    - Kelly, Orr, 1978, 2008 (Box 39)
    - Kelso, Arthur David, Jr., 1978, 1992 (Box 39)
    - Kempster, Norman, 1978, 2011 (Box 39)
    - Kiker, Douglas, 1978, 1991 (Box 40)
    - King, Brian B., 1978, 2008 (Box 40)
    - King, Seth S., 1978, 2007 (Box 40)
    - Kiplinger, Todd, 1978, 2008 (Box 40)
    - Kirkman, Donald, 1978, 2008 (Box 40)
    - Kirschten, Dick, 1978, 2009 (Box 40)
    - Klurfeld, James, 1978, 2007 (Box 40)
    - Knight, Louise W., 1978, 2007 (Box 40)
    - Knoller, Mark, 1978, 2007 (Box 40)
    - Kole, John, 1989, 2007 (Box 40)
    - Koppel, Ted, 1978, 2004-2009 (Box 40)
    - Koran, Nancy, 1978, 2006-2007 (Box 40)
    - Krause, Axel, 1978, 2007 (Box 40)
    - Kuckro, Rod, 1978, 2006-2007 (Box 40)
    - Lanouette, William, 1978, 1994-2006 (Box 40)
    - Law, Lou, 1978 (Box 40)
    - Lehner, Urban, 1978, 2006-2007 (Box 40)
    - Leonard, Mary, 1978, 2007 (Box 40)
    - Leubsdorf, Carl, 1978, 2006 See also Container 64 (Box 40)
    - Lewis, Finlay, 1978, 2006-2010 (Box 40)
    - Lewis, Robert, 1978, 2007 (Box 40)
    - Lilly, Judlyne, 1978, 2008 (Box 40)
    - Lindquist, Kirsten, 1978, 2009 (Box 40)
    - Lindsay, John, 1978, 1988 (Box 40)
    - Logan, Harold J., 1978, 2006-2012 (Box 40)
    - Long, Steven, 1978 (Box 40)
    - Lord, Mary, 1978, 2007-2012 (Box 40)
    - Lowenstein, Doug, 1978, 1987, 2007-2011 See also mss83739_163_001 (Box 40)
    - Lubar, Jeff, 1978, 2006-2010 (Box 41)
    - Lynch, Bill, 1978, 2007 (Box 41)
    - Lynch, David, 1978, 1999, 2008 (Box 41)
    - Maclean, John N., 1978, 2008 (Box 41)
    - Maitlin, Robert, 1978, 2008 (Box 41)
    - Malia, Thomas, 1978, 1999 (Box 41)
    - Maloy, Richard, 1978, 1987, 2006, 2014 (Box 41)
    - Margolis, Jon, 1978, 2007 (Box 41)
    - Marion, Larry, 1978, 2008 (Box 41)
    - Marro, Anthony, 1978, 2003-2007 (Box 41)
    - Mason, Vicky, 1978, 2007 (Box 41)
    - Masters, Kim, 1978, 2003-2010 (Box 41)
    - Mathis, Sue, 1978, 1985-1990 (Box 41)
    - Maxfield, David, 1978 (Box 41)
    - McCarthy, James [?], 1978 (Box 41)
    - McCartney, James H., 1978, 2007-2011 (Box 41)
    - McClain, Wallace, Jr., 1978 (Box 41)
    - McClung, John, 1978, 2007 (Box 41)
    - McConagha, Alan, 1978, 2011 (Box 41)
    - McDowell, Charles, 1978, 2010 (Box 41)
    - McFeatters, Dale, 1978, 2008 (Box 41)
    - McGuire, Frank G., 1978, 2007 (Box 41)
    - McMillion, Rhonda J., 1978, 2006 (Box 41)
    - McWethy, Jack, 1978, 2006-2008 (Box 41)
    - Mears, Walter R. (Walter Robert), 1978, 2005-2006 (Box 41)
    - Membrino, John, 1978, 2009 (Box 41)
    - Methvin, Eugene H., 1978, 2006-2012 (Box 41)
    - Miller, Judith, 1978, 2004-2009 (Box 41)
    - Miller, Loye, 1977-1978, 2008 (Box 41)
    - Miller, Peter G., 1978, 2010 (Box 41)
    - Miller, Theodore J., 1978 (Box 41)
    - Mills, Betty, 1978, 2009 (Box 41)
    - Mills, [J.], 1978 (Box 41)
    - Milne, John, 1978, 2008 (Box 41)
    - Mintz, Morton, 1978, 2006 (Box 42)
    - Miscellaneous notes, 2009 (Box 42)
    - Mochel, Patricia, 1978, 2009 (Box 42)
    - Morison, Robert, 1978, 2007-2010 (Box 42)
    - Morris, James, 1978 (Box 42)
    - Morse, Robert, 1978, 2008 (Box 42)
    - Morton, Bruce, 1978, 2005-2006, 2014 See also Container 65 (Box 42)
    - Mossberg, Walter S., 1978, 2007 (Box 42)
    - Moulton, Charlotte, 1978, 1991-1992, 2004-2008 (Box 42)
    - Myers, Lisa, 1978, 2005-2009 (Box 42)
    - Notes, 1977-1978, (2 folders) (Box 42)
    - Nease, Jack, 1978, 2007 (Box 42)
    - Nelson, W. Dale, 1978, 2007 (Box 42)
    - Neumann, Deanne, 1977 (Box 42)
    - Nickel, Herman W., 1978 (Box 42)
    - Nordlinger, Stephen, 1978, 2007 (Box 42)
    - Norman, Lloyd, 1978, 1987 (Box 42)
    - Oberdorfer, Don, 1978, 2006 See also mss83739_163_019 (Box 42)
    - O'Brien, Tim, 1978, 1999, 2007 (Box 43)
    - Ogden, Chris, 1978, 2007 (Box 43)
    - Olofson, Darwin, 1978, 2002 (Box 43)
    - Olson, Lynne, 1978, 2008-2011 See also mss83739_163_012 (Box 43)
    - Ordovensky, Pat, 1978, 2008 (Box 43)
    - O'Rourke, Lawrence M., 2010 (Box 43)
    - O'Shea, James E., 1978, 2009-2011 (Box 43)
    - Osmer McQuade, Margaret, 1978, 2007 (Box 43)
    - Ostroff, Jim, 1978, 2008 (Box 43)
    - Ostrow, Ronald J., 1978, 2007 (Box 43)
    - Pagano, Penny Girard, 1978, 2007 See also mss83739_163_013 (Box 43)
    - Pappas, Ike, 1978, 2006-2008 (Box 43)
    - Parker, Rich, 1978 (Box 43)
    - Parkhurst, Steven, 1978, 2007 (Box 43)
    - Parmenter, Cindy, 1978, 2007 (Box 43)
    - Patterson, Kathy, 1978, 2007 See also mss83739_163_013 (Box 43)
    - Paulson, Mort, 1978, 2008 (Box 43)
    - Payne, Richard, 1978, 2007 (Box 43)
    - Peterson, Bill, 1978, 1990 (Box 43)
    - Peterson, Roger, 1978, 2004 (Box 43)
    - Pianin, Eric, 1978, 2007 (Box 43)
    - Pierpoint, Robert, 1978, 2008-2011 (Box 43)
    - Pincus, Walter, 1978, 2006 (Box 43)
    - Plante, Bill, 1978, 2006 See also Container 66 (Box 43)
    - Poe, Edgar Allen, 2010 (Box 43)
    - Poole, Dan, 1978, 2007 (Box 43)
    - Pound, Ed, 1978, 2007-2009 (Box 43)
    - Putzel, Michael, 1978, 2007 (Box 43)
    - Quinlan, Mary Kay, 1978, 1987, 2007 (Box 43)
    - Quinn, Charles, 1978, 2007 (Box 43)
    - Rabb, Charles, 1978, 2008 (Box 43)
    - Raeke, Carolyn, 1978, 2009 (Box 44)
    - Ramsey, McClain, 1978, 1987, 1997 (Box 44)
    - Randal, Judith, 1978, 2005-2008 (Box 44)
    - Randolph, Eleanor, 1978, 2007 (Box 44)
    - Rankin, Robert, 1978, 2006-2009 (Box 44)
    - Reichmann, Jean, 1978 (Box 44)
    - Reid, T. R., 1978, 2007 (Box 44)
    - Reinhold, Robert, 1978, 1996 (Box 44)
    - Reynolds, Barbara A., 1978, 2009 (Box 44)
    - Richards, Bill, 1978, 2007 (Box 44)
    - Richards, Carol, 1978, 2007 (Box 44)
    - Risser, James V., 1977, 2007-2009 (Box 44)
    - Roberts, Steven V., 1978, 2007 See also mss83739_163_021 (Box 44)
    - Robinson, Marilyn, 1978 (Box 44)
    - Rodgers, Walter C., 1978, 2007 (Box 44)
    - Roper, James E., 1978, 1998, 2008 (Box 44)
    - Rose, Julia, 1978, 2009 (Box 44)
    - Rosenstein, Jay, 1978, 2005 (Box 44)
    - Rosenwasser, Marc, 1978, 2002-2007 (Box 44)
    - Roth, Richard, 1978, 2005-2007 (Box 44)
    - Rowe, James C., 1978, 2009 (Box 44)
    - Rowe, James L., 1978, 2001-2006 (Box 44)
    - Rubin, B. J., 1978 (Box 44)
    - Rutter, Judy Gardner, 1978, 2007 (Box 37)
    - Ryan, Richard, 1978, 2007 (Box 44)
    - Salditch, Martin, 1978, 1999 (Box 44)
    - Sanders, Donald, 1978-1979 (Box 44)
    - Sanoff, Alvin P., 1978, 2007 (Box 45)
    - Scanlan, Dan, 1978, 2006-2010 (Box 45)
    - Schakne, Robert, 1978, 1989, 2008 (Box 45)
    - Schwartz, Berl, 1978, 2002-2007 (Box 45)
    - Scott, Ivan, 1978, 2005-2008 See also Container 67 (Box 45)
    - Segall, J. Peter, 2004-2011 (Box 45)
    - Shabecoff, Philip, 1978, 2003-2008 (Box 45)
    - Shannon, Don, 1978, 2007 (Box 45)
    - Shannon, Elaine and Ted Gest, 1978, 2005-2008 See also Container 37 and See also mss83739_163_020 (Box 45)
    - Shepard, Alicia C., 1978, 2007-2008 See also mss83739_163_017 (Box 45)
    - Shields, Edward, 1978, 1993 (Box 45)
    - Shifrin, Carole, 1978, 2007 (Box 45)
    - Sibley, Martin, 1978, 2006 (Box 45)
    - Siddon, Arthur J., 1978, 1990 (Box 45)
    - Sidey, Hugh, 1978, 2005 (Box 45)
    - Simpson, Carole, 1978, 1992-2007 (Box 45)
    - Singer, James, 1978 (Box 45)
    - Sloyan, Patrick J., 1978, 2007 (Box 45)
    - Smith, A. Robert, 1978, 2001-2007 (Box 45)
    - Smith, Hedrick, 1978, 2007-2011 See also mss83739_163_015 (Box 45)
    - Smith, Karen Haas, 1978, 1991, 1998, 2009 (Box 45)
    - Smith, Sam, 1978, 2007-2011 (Box 45)
    - Smolka, Richard G., 1978, 2006-2013 (Box 45)
    - Spencer, Susan, 1978, 2001-2009 (Box 45)
    - Stanfield, Rochelle, 2005-2006 (Box 45)
    - Steele, Sally, 1978 (Box 45)
    - Steif, William, 1978, 2007-2008 (Box 45)
    - Stern, Carl, 1978, 2007 See also mss83739_163_007 (Box 46)
    - Stertz, Marc, 1978, 2006 (Box 46)
    - Strickland, Jean, 1978 (Box 46)
    - Strout, Richard L., 1978, 1990 (Box 46)
    - Stuart, Peter C., 1978, 2010-2011 (Box 46)
    - Sulkin, Sidney, 1978, 1992-1995, 2008 (Box 46)
    - Sullam, Brian, 1978, 2002-2006 (Box 46)
    - Sullivan, Scott G., 1978, 2006-2011 (Box 46)
    - Sutherland, John P. (Jack), 1978, 1988 (Box 46)
    - Swardson, Anne, 1978, 2006 (Box 46)
    - Taft, Dale R., 1978 (Box 46)
    - Thomas, Gary, 1978, 2007 (Box 46)
    - Thomas, Jo, 1978, 2007 (Box 46)
    - Thompson, Alan, 1978 (Box 46)
    - Thompson, Stephen, 1978 (Box 46)
    - Thomsen, Dietrick E., 1978, 1988 (Box 46)
    - Thornton, Lee, 1978, 2007-2013 (Box 46)
    - Toedtman, James, 1978, 2007 (Box 46)
    - Tolchin, Martin, 1978, 2001, 2007 See also mss83739_163_009 (Box 46)
    - Tuthill, Mary, 1978 (Box 46)
    - Uliano, Richard, 1978, 2007 (Box 46)
    - Underwood, Doug, 1978, 2007 (Box 46)
    - Van Riper, Frank, 1978, 2009 (Box 46)
    - Verbrycke, Pamela P., 1978 (Box 46)
    - Volz, Joe, 1978, 2009 (Box 46)
    - Waggoner, Glenn, 1978, 2006 (Box 46)
    - Wagy, Norman, 1978, 1987, 2007 (Box 46)
    - Walczak, Leon, 1978, 2008 (Box 46)
    - Waldman, Myron S., 1978, 1993 (Box 46)
    - Walker, Janet, 1978, 2006 (Box 46)
    - Wallach, John, 1978, 2002, 2008 (Box 46)
    - Walters, Phil, 1978, 1999 (Box 46)
    - Ward, Morris A., 1978, 2007 (Box 46)
    - Warren, Ellen, 1978, 2005-2007 (Box 47)
    - Waters, Robert, 1978, 2007 (Box 47)
    - Watson, Jerome, 1978, 1993 (Box 47)
    - Weaver, Warren, 1978, 1997, 2008 (Box 47)
    - Wehr, Elizabeth, 1978, 2007 (Box 47)
    - Wellborn, Stan, 1978, 2006 (Box 47)
    - Wells, Betty, 1978, 2007 (Box 47)
    - Wermiel, Steve, 1978, 2006 (Box 47)
    - Westlein, Patricia Rose, 1978, 2008 (Box 47)
    - Wiese, Arthur E., 1978, 2007, 2016 (Box 47)
    - Wilkie, Curtis, 1978, 2007 (Box 47)
    - Williams, Betty Anne, 1978, 2007 (Box 47)
    - Wiper, Roberta, 1978 (Box 47)
    - Wolman, Jonathan, 1978, 2008 (Box 47)
    - Woodruff, Judy, 1978, 2005 (Box 47)
    - Wordham, Bill, 1977-1978, 1993, 2004 (Box 47)
    - Yoder, Allan, 1978, 1992 (Box 47)
    - Young, Leah, 1978, 2006 (Box 47)
    - Young, Robert, 1978, 2000 (Box 47)
    - Zimmerman, Bill, 1978, 2007 (Box 47)
    - Zimmerman, Richard G., 1978, 2008 (Box 47)
    - Zuckerman, Ed, 1978, 2005, 2011 (Box 47)
  - Reporters demographic data, 1998, (2 folders) (Box 47)
  - Reporters demographic data, 1998, (2 folders) (Box 48)
  - Senate committee hearings on television, 1979-1984, (3 folders) (Box 48)
  - Senate notes, articles, and press releases, 1984, (3 folders) (Box 49)
  - Senate staff survey, 1984 (Box 49)
  - Standing committee of correspondents, 1979-1984, (3 folders) (Box 49)
  - Television news content study, 1994, (3 folders) (Box 50)
  - Through Their Eyes: Foreign Correspondents in the United States
    - Articles, 1975-2005, (2 folders) (Box 50)
    - "Borrowed News and the Internet," 1999-2005, (1 folder) (Box 50)
    - "Borrowed News and the Internet," 1999-2005, (1 folder) (Box 51)
    - Chapter Four: Patterns, 1999-2005, (3 folders) (Box 51)
    - Chapter Five: Irregulars, 1999-2005, (3 folders) (Box 51)
    - Chapter Five: Irregulars, 1999-2005, (1 folder) (Box 52)
    - Chapter Six: Hollywood, 1999-2005, (4 folders) (Box 52)
    - Chapter Seven: In America, 1999-2005, (2 folders) (Box 53)
    - Chapter Eight: Time, 2002-2005 (Box 53)
    - Chapter Nine: Contact, the CNN Effect, 2002-2005 (Box 53)
    - Chapter Ten: Access to Government, 2002-2005, (2 folders) (Box 53)
    - Draft, Mar./Apr. 2005 (Box 53)
    - Foreign embassies, undated, (3 folders) (Box 54)
    - "Help," 1986-2005, (4 folders) (Box 54)
    - "The Home Angle," 1982-2001, (2 folders) (Box 55)
    - Interviews by country, 1999-2003, (5 folders) (Box 55)
    - Interviews by country, 1999-2003, (3 folders) (Box 56)
    - Nelson, Anne, Columbia University School of Journalism, 2001-2002, (2 folders) (Box 56)
    - New York Times news summary, 1999 (Box 56)
    - Newswork project proposal, 1982-2005, (3 folders) (Box 57)
    - "Now," 2001-2005 (Box 57)
    - "One Day [Last Story]," 1999-2005, (3 folders) (Box 57)
    - "One Day [Last Story]," 1999-2005, (1 folder) (Box 58)
    - Russian correspondents in Washington, D.C., 2001-2003 (Box 58)
    - Studies of foreign correspondents, 1981-1983 (Box 58)
    - Survey data analysis, 1999-2003, (2 folders) (Box 58)
    - Surveys of foreign correspondents in New York, Chicago, and Los Angeles, 1999 (Box 58)
  - Washington, D.C. reporters
    - Interviews
      - "A-Z" interview list, 2005-2006 (Box 59)
      - "A" transcripts, 2005-2006 (Box 59)
      - Abbott, Chuck, 2005 (Box 59)
      - Ackerman, Andrew, 2006 (Box 59)
      - Ackerman, Tom, 2005 (Box 59)
      - Alexander, Andrew, 2006 See also Container 32, See also mss83739_163_028, See also mss83739_163_029, and See also mss83739_163_027 (Box 59)
      - Arenstein, Howard, 2005 (Box 59)
      - Aubrey, Allison, 2006 (Box 59)
      - Augenstein, Neal, 2005 (Box 59)
      - Avellino, Jennifer, 2006 (Box 59)
      - "B" transcripts, 2005-2006, (2 folders) (Box 59)
      - Babington, Charles, 2006 (Box 59)
      - Baier, Bret, 2005 (Box 59)
      - Baker, Cissy, 2006 (Box 59)
      - Baker, Peter, 2006 (Box 59)
      - Banales, Jorge Jr., undated (Box 59)
      - Banville, Lee, 2006 (Box 59)
      - Barnes, Fred, 2005 (Box 59)
      - Barnes, Julian, 2006 (Box 59)
      - Barnett, Jim, 2005 (Box 59)
      - Barton, Paul C., 2005 (Box 59)
      - Beinart, Peter, 2005 (Box 59)
      - Benedetto, Richard, 2005 (Box 59)
      - Berardelli, Phil, 2005 (Box 59)
      - Birnbaum, Jeffrey H., 2005 (Box 59)
      - Bishop, Sam, 2005 (Box 59)
      - Biskupic, Joan, 2006 (Box 59)
      - Bjerga, Alan, 2005 (Box 59)
      - Bohannon, Camille, 2006 (Box 59)
      - Boilen, Bob, 2006 (Box 59)
      - Boliek, Brooks, 2005 (Box 59)
      - Borger, Gloria, 2005 (Box 59)
      - Bowman, Tom, 2006 (Box 59)
      - Brennan, Christine, 2005 (Box 60)
      - Bridis, Ted, 2005 (Box 60)
      - Brumfiel, Geoff, 2005 (Box 60)
      - Bumiller, Elisabeth, 2005 (Box 60)
      - Burger, Tim, 2004 (Box 60)
      - Burns, Robert, 2005 See also Container 34 (Box 60)
      - "C" transcripts, 2005-2006, (2 folders) (Box 60)
      - Calmes, Jackie, 2005 (Box 60)
      - Canning, Andrea, 2006 (Box 60)
      - Carney, James, 2006 (Box 60)
      - Cassata, Donna, 2005 (Box 60)
      - Chapman, Irv, 2005 (Box 60)
      - Chen, Edwin, 2005 (Box 60)
      - Chen, Joie, 2005 (Box 60)
      - Chung, Linda, 2006 (Box 60)
      - Clapman, Leah, 2006 (Box 60)
      - Connolly, Ceci, 2005 (Box 60)
      - Corke, Kevin, 2006 (Box 60)
      - Cornwell, Susan, 2005 (Box 60)
      - Costello, Tom, 2005 (Box 60)
      - Crea, Joe, 2005 (Box 60)
      - Crowley, Candy, 2005 (Box 60)
      - Crystal, Lester M., 2006 (Box 60)
      - Cullum, Blanquita, 2006 (Box 60)
      - Cummings, Jeanne, 2006 (Box 60)
      - "D" transcripts, 2005-2006 (Box 61)
      - Daly, Matthew, 2006 (Box 61)
      - Davenport, Anne, 2005 (Box 61)
      - de Vogue, Ariane, 2006 (Box 61)
      - Deaner, Sonja, 2006 (Box 61)
      - Deans, Bob, 2006 (Box 61)
      - DeBose, Brian, 2005 (Box 61)
      - Dine, Philip M., 2005 (Box 61)
      - Drinkard, Jim, 2006 (Box 61)
      - Drummond, Steve, 2005 (Box 61)
      - Dunlavey, Dennis, 2005 (Box 61)
      - Durham, Deborah, undated (Box 61)
      - "E" transcripts, 2005-2008 (Box 61)
      - Eisele, Albert, 2006 See also mss83739_163_040 (Box 61)
      - Elfin, Dana and Harold Pskowski, 2008 See also mss83739_163_041 (Box 61)
      - Elving, Ronald D., 2005 See also mss83739_163_042 (Box 61)
      - Ensor, David, 2006 (Box 61)
      - Epstein, Edward, 2005 (Box 61)
      - Erickson, Charlie, 2005 (Box 61)
      - "F" transcripts, 2005-2006 (Box 61)
      - Farrell, Kate, 2005 (Box 61)
      - Feeney, Susan and Steve Hirsh, 2006 (Box 61)
      - Ferguson, Ellyn, 2005 (Box 61)
      - Ferry, David, 2006 (Box 61)
      - Fitzgerald, Gena, 2006 (Box 61)
      - Flores-Hurley, Katrina, 2006 (Box 61)
      - Fournier, Ron, 2006 (Box 61)
      - Freedberg, Sydney J., Jr., 2005 (Box 61)
      - Funk, Tim, 2005 (Box 61)
      - Fuss, Bob, 2006 (Box 62)
      - "G" transcripts, 2005-2006 (Box 62)
      - Gambrell, Kathy, 2005 (Box 62)
      - Getler, Michael, 2006 (Box 62)
      - Geyer, Georgie Anne, 2005 (Box 62)
      - Gibson, William, undated (Box 62)
      - Gilgoff, Dan, 2006 (Box 62)
      - Glass, Evan, 2005 (Box 62)
      - Goldfarb, Michael, Katherine Mangu-Ward, and Reihan Salam, undated (Box 62)
      - Goldfein, Mike, undated (Box 62)
      - Goldstein, David, 2005 (Box 62)
      - Goldstein, Steve, 2005 (Box 62)
      - Gordon, Michael R., 2006 (Box 62)
      - Gosselin, Peter G., 2005 (Box 62)
      - Graff, Garrett M., 2005 (Box 62)
      - Groppe, Maureen, 2006 (Box 62)
      - Gurdon, Hugo, undated (Box 62)
      - "H" transcripts, 2004-2006, (2 folders) (Box 62)
      - Halperin, Mark, 2005 (Box 62)
      - Hanner, Mark, 2005 (Box 62)
      - Hannon, Tom, 2006 (Box 62)
      - Harris, Ron, 2005 (Box 62)
      - Hart, Brooke, 2005 (Box 63)
      - Harwood, John, undated (Box 63)
      - Havemann, Joel, 2006 (Box 63)
      - Hawke, Anne, 2004 (Box 63)
      - Hearn, Josephine, 2005 (Box 63)
      - Hedges, Mike, 2006 (Box 63)
      - Heller, Marc, 2005 (Box 63)
      - Henderson, Stephen, 2006 (Box 63)
      - Hendin, Robert, 2006 (Box 63)
      - Henning, Marcia, 2006 (Box 63)
      - Hill, Patrice, 2005 (Box 63)
      - Holland, Gina, 2006 (Box 63)
      - Holland, Jesse J., 2005 (Box 63)
      - Hopkins, Cheyenne, undated (Box 63)
      - Hume, Brit, 2005 See also Container 39 and See also mss83739_163_003 (Box 63)
      - "J" transcripts, 2005-2006 (Box 63)
      - Jacobson, Lou, 2006 (Box 63)
      - James, Frank, 2005 (Box 63)
      - Jansen, Lesa, undated (Box 63)
      - Javers, Eamon, 2005 (Box 63)
      - Jenning, Linda Kramer, 2005 (Box 63)
      - Jensen, Kristin, 2006 (Box 63)
      - Johnson, Jeff, 2005 (Box 63)
      - Johnson, Sandy, 2005 (Box 63)
      - Johnson, Sasha, 2005 (Box 63)
      - Johnston, David Cay, 2005 (Box 63)
      - "K" transcripts, 2005-2006, (2 folders) (Box 63)
      - Kammer, Jerry, 2006 (Box 63)
      - Kaplan, Jonathan, 2005 (Box 64)
      - Karl, Jonathan, 2005 (Box 64)
      - Keane, Angela Greiling, 2005 (Box 64)
      - Keil, Richard, 2006 (Box 64)
      - Kelley, Matthew, 2005 (Box 64)
      - Kelly, Greg, 2005 (Box 64)
      - Kelly, Nancy E., 2005 (Box 64)
      - Kemper, Bob, 2006 (Box 64)
      - Kessler, Glenn, 2005 (Box 64)
      - Kingsbury, Alex, 2005 (Box 64)
      - Kiplinger, Knight A., 2007 See also mss83739_163_035 (Box 64)
      - Kitfield, James, 2006 (Box 64)
      - Koff, Stephen, 2005 (Box 64)
      - Kole, Tom, undated (Box 64)
      - Kronholz, June, 2006 (Box 64)
      - Kumar, Dinesh, 2006 (Box 64)
      - "L" transcripts, 2005-2006 (Box 64)
      - Lamb, Brian, 2006 (Box 64)
      - Landay, Jonathan, 2004 (Box 64)
      - Lane, Charles, 2006 (Box 64)
      - Langmade, Brigette, 2005 (Box 64)
      - Leubsdorf, Carl, 2005 See also Container 40 (Box 64)
      - Lieberman, Brett, 2005 (Box 64)
      - Lightman, David, 2005 (Box 64)
      - Lindell, Chuck, 2005 (Box 64)
      - Lipman, Larry, 2005 (Box 64)
      - Lizza, Ryan, 2005 (Box 64)
      - Lochhead, Carolyn, 2005 (Box 64)
      - Loomans, Kathryn, 2006 (Box 64)
      - Lorente, Rafael, 2005 (Box 65)
      - Lorenzo, Aaron, 2005 (Box 65)
      - "M" transcripts, 2005-2006, (2 folders) (Box 65)
      - Machacek, John, 2005 (Box 65)
      - Maer, Peter, 2005 (Box 65)
      - Majchrowitz, Mike, 2005 (Box 65)
      - Matus, Victorino, 2005 (Box 65)
      - Mazzetti, Mark, undated (Box 65)
      - McCutcheon, Chuck, 2005 (Box 65)
      - McGuire, Dave, 2005 (Box 65)
      - McLure, Jake, 2006 (Box 65)
      - McMillen, Robert, 2005 (Box 65)
      - Meckler, Laura, 2006 (Box 65)
      - Medrano, Manuel, 2006 (Box 65)
      - Meek, James Gordon, 2006 (Box 65)
      - Melendez, Michele, undated (Box 65)
      - Meserve, Jeanne, 2006 (Box 65)
      - Meyer, Lisa, 2006 (Box 65)
      - Milbank, Dana, 2006 (Box 65)
      - Miller, David, 2006 (Box 65)
      - Mohammed, Valencia, 2005 (Box 65)
      - Moniz, Dave, 2005 (Box 65)
      - Morton, Bruce, 2005 See also Container 42 (Box 65)
      - Mui, Ylan, 2006 (Box 65)
      - Mundy, Alicia, 2005 (Box 65)
      - "N" transcripts, 2005-2006 (Box 65)
      - Neal, Terry, 2005 (Box 65)
      - Nesmith, Jeff, 2006 (Box 65)
      - Neuman, Johanna, 2005 (Box 65)
      - Nichols, Hans, 2005 (Box 65)
      - Noguchi, Yuki, 2006 (Box 66)
      - "O" transcripts, 2005-2006 (Box 66)
      - O'Connor, Phil, 2006 (Box 66)
      - Ognanovich, Nancy, 2006 (Box 66)
      - Overby, Peter, 2005 (Box 66)
      - "P" transcripts, 2006-2005 (Box 66)
      - Pace, David, 2006 (Box 66)
      - Palca, Joe, 2006 (Box 66)
      - Palmer, Kimberly, 2005 (Box 66)
      - Patton, Oliver, 2005 (Box 66)
      - Peck, Louis, undated (Box 66)
      - Perry, Andrea, 2006 (Box 66)
      - Plante, Bill, 2006 See also Container 43 (Box 66)
      - Potts, Tracie, 2006 (Box 66)
      - Prah, Pamela, 2005 (Box 66)
      - Price, Deb, 2006 (Box 66)
      - Pusey, Allen, 2006 (Box 66)
      - Puzzanghera, James, 2005 (Box 66)
      - "R" transcripts, 2005-2006 (Box 66)
      - Ratliff, Walter, 2005 (Box 66)
      - Ratner, Victor, 2006 (Box 66)
      - Raviv, Dan, 2005 (Box 66)
      - Reid, Chip, 2005 (Box 66)
      - Ridgeway, James, 2005 (Box 66)
      - Roberts, Ju-Don Marshall, 2005 (Box 66)
      - Roberts, Nathan, 2005 (Box 66)
      - Rosen, James, 2005 See also mss83739_163_022 (Box 66)
      - Rosenberg, Howard L., undated (Box 66)
      - "S" transcripts, 2005-2006, (2 folders) (Box 66)
      - Sammon, Bill, undated (Box 67)
      - Sanchez, Marcela, undated (Box 67)
      - Sarasohn, Judy, 2005 (Box 67)
      - Savage, David G., 2006 (Box 67)
      - Schmitt, Eric, 2005 (Box 67)
      - Schultz, Teri, 2006 (Box 67)
      - Scott, Ivan, 2005 See also Container 45 (Box 67)
      - Seabrook, Andrea, 2005 (Box 67)
      - Segraves, Mark, 2005 (Box 67)
      - Serafini, Marilyn, 2006 (Box 67)
      - Shanker, Thom, 2005 (Box 67)
      - Sharon, Adam, undated (Box 67)
      - Sherman, Mark, 2005 (Box 67)
      - Shesgreen, Deirdre, 2006 (Box 67)
      - Siegel, Robert, 2006 (Box 67)
      - Silva, Mark, 2006 (Box 67)
      - Silver, Marc, 2005 (Box 67)
      - Skiba, Katherine M., 2006 (Box 67)
      - Smith, Stephanie, 2006 (Box 67)
      - Smith, Stephen G., undated See also mss83739_163_016 (Box 67)
      - Solomon, Deborah, 2005 (Box 67)